So , um , the little key is for the lock up top .
And the one for below .
You 're not staying ?
No , I prefer not to . Too many memories .
It 's good for you ?
Yeah , of course . I understand .
- See you later . - Okay .
Lewis ?
Lewis , is that you ?
Lewis !
Translation and subtitles by PEPPER LALASPAIN * * * SONG LIVES FOR EVER * * *
Maureen ?
I dont know ... I fell asleep .
So ?
There was a presence .
I felt something . I just can 't ...
I can 't tell , it was too far .
You must make contact .
I think there might need to be two of us for that .
There ... There wasn 't enough pull .
Because I felt something . It was just keeping its distance .
Come here .
You see the cross ?
Yeah .
Has that always been there ?
She said that she couldn 't make a contact .
Does she still feel a presence ?
Yes , she says the house is inhabited .
Well , we can 't buy unless we 're sure .
We need to know if it 's benevolent or not .
It 's too much of an investment .
Hey ... um ... So , there ...
Could be no one .
But there could be something . I-I just need more time , I think .
It 's extremely difficult to find a portal into the spiritual world .
It 's the way that it is .
I was in Stockholm last week ,
I saw a wonderful exhibition at the Modern Art Museum .
Hilma af Klint .
Have you ever heard of her ?
Mm ... no .
She says that spirits
commission her paintings .
She invented abstract art
before Kandinsky and Malevitch in 1906 .
She says that
the spirit-world communicated with us .
Through her .
Hilma af Klint .
ABSTRACTION
PIONEER
What fascinated me when I discovered Hilma af Klint 's work was ...
That these grand and enigmatic paintings
had been painted in the early 1900 's .
And that they were made by a Swedish female artist
that I hadn 't heard about before .
Maybe the most fascinating part is that these pieces
were made before the conception of abstract art .
But Hilma af Klint kept her art secret ,
She was sure that they wouldn 't be understood during her life .
In her will she decided that they would
be kept hidden until 20 years after her death .
So , a century ago , Hilma af Klint
painted for the future .
And the future is here now .
Are you okay ?
It didn 't bore you too much at reception ?
No , no more than normal . I lost my passport .
How long will she be in Milan for ?
Two days .
I put everything on a rack .
Here are the leather pants from the new collection .
They 're Kyra 's style . I mean , I can see her in them .
Are we able to cut them ? Is it possible ? They 'll be too big .
Let me look into this .
I 'll get them for you from the studio .
I 'm not really supposed to , but ...
Please , you bring them back as soon as you can ,
otherwise I will be in big trouble .
Of course .
She 's going to need something a little flashier for the Amfar dinner .
Yeah .
That 's the stuff Louis set aside for the dinner .
If Louis likes it , then she 'll love it .
- You like it ? - Mm .
So does Louis . It 's not easy to wear .
It 's sensual and strong .
- I 'll take it , and some boots . - Okay .
I think I 'll take both bags and this belt .
You know her . Don 't want to risk it .
Kyra would want the brown , for sure .
Or the blue . Or neither .
Ah , she gave me a blank check .
- Do ... do you take deposits ? - Yes .
Yes .
- She wants 4,500 . - Cool .
500 for the belt , and 2,000 for each bag .
Great .
Maureen , I got back but I have to leave right away .
We 'll miss each other . I 'm off to Milan tomorrow morning .
I 'm leaving an envelope with what I owe you for the last two weeks .
Take care . Kyra .
PS : I left my Mac on the desk .
Can you do the upgrade for me ?
Hilma af Klint has moved in spiritual circles
and participated in séances ,
later also she was a medium .
What actually is regarded as the essence of spiritualism ?
Well , the central idea of spiritualism ,
is the idea that there is a world beyond our world .
And spiritualists try to give empirical proof of this world .
In 1848 ,
the Fox sisters heard rappings
and they interpreted these rappings as messages from deceased persons .
And that was for them real proof
of the existence of a higher world beyond our world .
It 's interesting that the Moriset code had been invented 2 years earlier .
The spiritualists were always very close to the technological avant-garde .
For example , the first abstract photographs
have been taken by spiritualists .
Hilma af Klint believed that she received the abstract paintings
from higher levels of consciousness .
When she started to paint as a medium ,
she rejected the skills she had learned at the art academy .
And that was due to the influence of spiritualism and theosophy .
Now you mentioned theosophy ,
What was Rudolf Steiner 's view on abstract art ?
Steiner rejected abstract paintings .
But that 's not the whole story ...
- Hey . - I 've been trying to reach you for a week .
I know . I 've been working .
A lot .
Sorry .
How 's it going with Kyra ?
Ah ... I never see her .
We leave each other messages .
I hate this job , actually .
I fucking hate her . She 's a ...
That 's not what you said before .
Yeah I was just happy to stay in Paris and pay my rent .
Yeah , well , what 's changed ?
I spend my days doing bullshit .
That doesn 't interest me , and it keeps me from what does .
It 's driving me fucking crazy .
You should come here .
Yeah , to the Sultanate of Oman ?
I 'll be here another two months .
I thought you were almost done ?
I finished reconfiguring the embassy 's computer system
and now I 'm just waiting for the security protocols .
When do you think you 'll get those ?
It could be tomorrow , could be next month ...
And once I get them I start the installing and configure them .
Come to Muscat !
Look , I came to the seaside for the weekend .
- Wow . - It 's beautiful .
What the hell would I do in Muscat ?
What the hell you do in Paris ?
You know .
I 'm waiting . I have to wait .
It 's been three months .
I think I felt something .
I need to go back to Lewis ' house . I really think I felt something .
You think you felt something or you 're sure ?
I just need to see it to the end . That 's all .
This is perfect . This works . Thank you .
This too .
I see this ...
Actually it may be perfect .
I 'd like to see them on you .
You don 't want to try them on ?
I ... you know that I can 't .
But you want to .
Sure , I mean .. if you could keep your mouth shut , maybe ...
but you totally dicked me over the last time I did it .
Try on the shoes at least . I 'll get them .
They 're the same size . She won 't have to send them back .
Okay , Vincent ...
You have to promise me ...
Not one word . Not one word .
My lips are sealed .
Really ?
If there 's traffic , there 's traffic . Nothing you can do about it .
They 'll wait .
They just need a little daylight . It 's okay .
No , I can 't wait . I have an appointment .
I 'll meet you at your place later this afternoon ?
Okay .
The leather pants ? They 're great , right ?
No , not these .. you can 't keep ... I promised ...
I promised that I 'd bring them back in the morning .
Please don 't do that to me .
I 'm telling them right now . It 's no problems . Don 't worry . Okay .
Hey so , she is on her way . She 's late . Her plane from Milan was just delayed .
But where is she ?
She 's on a highway . There 's traffic , apparently .
Can you stand in for her ? It 'll save some time .
I have to leave at four o 'clock .
Yeah , that 's okay . It 's perfect . Come .
You think she 'll ditch everything ?
Yeah , she 'll ditch everything . I brought you three options though so ...
With that we 'll make it through ?
I can 't make any promises .
I 'd feel more comfortable if you stayed .
You scared of Kyra ?
I hear she 's a monster .
This is your left ventricle .
It 's just slightly larger in size .
It was exactly the same for your twin brother .
You can live with it and die at 100 .
Or at 27 .
I treated Lewis just like I treated you .
An ultrasound twice a year .
There was no sign . Nothing .
One day , it just gave way .
Don 't be scared , Maureen . What happened to Lewis is very exceptional .
You can get up .
Everything is fine .
You just need to keep avoiding both intense physical efforts
and extreme emotions .
Like Lewis did ...
- I mean , ... he built cabinets . - I know .
He wanted to turn the house into a studio where he could teach
and practice carpentry .
He really considered it his future .
I 'll see you again in six months ?
I have no idea where I 'm going to be in six months .
Good evening , Maureen .
Excuse me , we haven 't met .
I 'm Ingo .
Hi ! Um , sorry ...
Is Kyra here ?
In her room with her lawyer .
They 've been on a conference call for an hour .
Problems with the foundation .
I 'm just here to pick up a few things . She 's aware .
Do you know where they are ?
There is one garment bag over there .
Um , random question , but
do you happen to know about two pairs of leather pants ?
They should be in the bag .
She wants to keep them .
Oh .
Okay .
She 's just in there ?
Ah , she 's a real fucking pain-in-the-ass , right ?
We 've been working on this for six months .
We can 't just call off the press trip at the last minute .
Hey Kyra ?
We have a 2-year-old gorilla who 's been gone for three weeks .
And now we have a problem with the whole family .
Mrs. Gellman 's husband invests a lot of time and money
into gorilla habitat preservation .
He cares deeply about gorillas .
But if things go wrong ,
this reflects really badly on his business interests ...
Hey Kyra , can I just ask you one quick q ...
This is serious . You need to take care of this .
Hello ?
The female is aggressive .
The male , Ngabo , you 've dealt with him is becoming aggressive .
Ngabo can become very aggressive in stressful situations .
I remember very well , thank you .
Where are they now ? Where are the gorillas ?
They wander off further and further into the mountains
and it 's difficult to monitor them .
We can 't cancel the reporters !
We have contractual obligations . We need those gorillas to be there .
Just one quick question ?
I 'm hearing problems , I 'm not hearing solutions .
Mind if I smoke ?
You have nothing better to do besides dress Kyra ?
Really find it worthy of your time ?
Do you have a better offer ?
Not exactly .
I 'm a correspondent for Men 's Vogue in Berlin .
I can put in a word for you .
Thank you .
But I .. you know , magazines aren 't really my thing .
They sell shit .
Mainly for advertisers , rather than readers .
So what ? You already have a stupid job .
It wouldn 't change a thing but ,
it pays better .
Not for me .
Some highly-regarded photographers publish in fashion magazines .
Are they free ?
I suppose so .
They get to choose their brands and subjects they shoot ?
No , that 's correct .
I don 't really see the freedom in that .
Yeah , I 'm going to go .
I 'll take the dress and the bags .
You really need to tell her she 's gotta return those pants .
I 'll come back tomorrow .
You know she 'll be here tomorrow ?
Ask her .
She 'll tell me to leave .
And you 're not leaving ?
I 'm waiting for her to finish . I want to speak with her .
She wants to dump me .
How long 's it been ?
Two years .
But she 's scared her husband will find out .
I 'm sure he suspects something .
You in love with her ?
Love ?
It never crossed my mind , no .
It 's just physical .
What are you doing in Paris ?
I 'm ... waiting .
I 'm gonna go .
What are you waiting for ?
My ... uh ... brother died here .
My twin brother ,
died in Paris .
An accident ?
No .
A heart attack .
I actually have the same ...
malformation .
Does it scare you ?
No .
And it didn 't scare him .
You stay here to mourn .
No , I 'm waiting .
I told you I was waiting .
What are you waiting for ?
So , we made this oath .
Whoever died first would send the other a sign .
A sign ?
From the afterlife ?
You could call it that . You could call it a million things .
But how will you know it 's a sign ?
I 'm a medium .
He was a medium .
I 'll just know it .
Have you communicated with spirits before ?
Lewis thought there were ... spirits . I 'm less sure .
But ... y-yes .
Somewhat .
There are invisible presences ...
around us , always .
Whether or not they 're the souls of the dead , I don 't know , but ...
When you 're a medium , you just are attuned to a certain ...
vibe .
What do you mean by , vibe ?
It 's an intuition thing . It 's a feeling you ...
You see this door ...
It 's only like slightly ajar .
I also this that ...
the soul ...
continues to exist after death .
I don 't really know if I believe in that .
But Lewis did .
And I have to give his spirit ...
whatever you want to call it ...
a chance to prove him right .
Until when ?
I had a sign .
- Oh ? - Yeah !
Are you sure ?
No . That 's why I 'm still waiting .
And then ?
Then I guess I 'll live my life .
Let it go .
I 'll come for you in the morning .
- Or before . Call when you want . - Okay .
Thank you .
So we thought about it , and we 're renovating .
I think that 's what Lewis would have wanted .
I just wanted Maureen to be at peace with this place .
And with Lewis ' spirit .
I ... I just wanted to say one last ...
Lewis would have been very happy that this house is yours again ...
And I 'm very glad too .
Now , it 's your house and ...
I 'll forget it .
Come on .
I need more from you .
I 'm gonna need more from you .
Give me one more sign .
Anything .
Give me the tiniest thing .
Is that it ? Is that it ?
Just the tiniest little thing ...
Is it that you can see me , you cannot talk to me ?
Because I don 't care what you do with the fucking plumbing .
I need you to fucking talk to me !
Please , I don 't understand .
You 're not my brother .
Unknown : I know you .
Unknown : And you know me .
Unknown : You 're off to London .
Who is this ?
Unknown : Have a guess .
No , answer my question .
Are you a man or a woman ?
Unknown : What difference does it make ?
Are you real ?
Are you alive or dead ?
Alive or dead ?
Lewis ?
Airplane Mode : On .
Unknown : I want you .
Stop .
I want you and I will have you .
How did you get this number ?
I 'm blocking you .
You don 't want to know who I am anymore ?
Unknown : I 'm here . I 'm watching you .
Unknown : I 'm kidding . I 'm not there .
Unknown : But I may be in London .
Unknown : You want to know where ?
Where ?
Thanks for answering .
I won 't be in London .
Are you relieved ?
Or disappointed ?
What do you want ?
You .
Not physically .
To make contact .
First .
I 've prepared everything Kyra asked for .
Two dresses she picked from the photograph ,
and a third one that didn 't photograph so well but I think she 'll like it .
Which one ?
This one there .
It 's silk organza .
In a photo you lose some of the sheen but ,
It really plays well with the light .
Oh yeah , it 's cool .
It 's really cool .
The harness comes in different colours as well .
- Can I see them ? - Yeah .
There you go . We 've got gold , black and nude .
In black .
Not for all tastes , but I think it 'll look amazing with Kyra .
Do you want to try it ?
Come .
Unknown : I suggest a game .
I hate games .
Sorry .
You want to try the dress ?
No , I 'll take it in two colours so that she has the option .
Cool . I 'll get it all packed up for you .
Unknown : Then not a game . Something else .
Meaning ?
Are you waiting for your train ?
Yes .
So answer my questions .
Do you want to be someone else ?
Yes .
Who ?
I don 't know .
I can 't know for you .
Tell me something you find unsettling .
Horror movies .
Why ?
A woman runs from a killer and hides .
What you find unsettling is fear .
Are you often scared ?
No .
Unknown number
I 'm on the train .
I 'll drop the stuff off this evening .
When do you get back ?
Even if it 's early afternoon ,
It 's okay . It 'll be ready for you in a garment bag .
I have to pick up the jewellery from Cartier ,
but everything , they said , is ready .
I would prefer it in euros if that 's not a problem ...
You know you could ask your driver to stop at an ATM on the way back from CTG .
It 'll take two seconds .
It was 400 .
We agreed on 400 .
There are a couple of taxi receipts as well .
See you tomorrow .
Yesterday , I tried on the shoes of the woman I work for .
Why are you telling me ?
Because she wouldn 't let me try them on .
So the answer is what 's forbidden ?
No desire if it 's not forbidden .
What else is forbidden ?
Unknown : Answering my questions ?
Yes .
Unknown : Are you back ?
Your place ?
Kyra 's ?
How do you know ?
You want to try on Kyra 's dresses ?
Yep .
Because it is forbidden ?
I did it .
You 're scared .
Yeah I am .
I thought you wanted to be someone else .
How are you ?
You 're sure the spirit isn 't there , anymore ?
Yes .
She vomited this ectoplasm
and left .
And the ectoplasm lingered for a minute ,
or less and then also disappeared .
Do you have an idea of what she wanted ?
She was really angry . Very violent .
Maybe she had a score to settle .
I think she was lost .
I don 't think she wants to come back . I don 't think she 'll be there again .
And what about Lewis ?
It 's been 95 days .
Jérôme and Cassandre are getting the bigger house .
Good .
You know , Lewis really loved them so that 's ...
perfect .
What about you ?
What 'll you do with the money ?
Nothing .
I don 't know .
I 'm not sure I can buy something else .
I 'm not confident enough about the future .
I feel you .
I don 't think you understand .
I definitely understand . Trust me .
I met someone .
You met some ... , like you ...
Oh !
Look ,
You must 've known them before .
Well , kind of ...
A friend of a friend .
After Lewis died , he reached out to me ,
and we grew closer .
You 're shocked .
No . Good . I think it 's ...
I was expecting it but like , of course .
I 'll always love Lewis ,
but I can 't spend my life in mourning .
I 'm not interested in mourning ,
Like suffering in pain , I 've had enough .
I think now I want life .
The other day , you said
Victor Hugo actu ... you know , you said that he communicated with spirits ...
What did you mean by that ? Like actually talked to them ?
When he was exiled in Jersey , he turned tables .
Like he conversed with famous historical figures like ,
even biblical ones .
It 's pretty out there .
How ?
I don 't really know .
I mean literally . Like verbally or with an alphabet ?
No , no , not the alphabet . They tried , but the spirit refused .
So what did he do ?
With a pedestal table .
The leg would tap on the floor like , once for " yes " , twice for " no " .
Like one for " A " , two for " B " and so on like ,
26 for " Z " .
That would take an unbelievable amount of time .
Yeah . There were pages and pages of transcriptions .
Well , that 's gotta be bullshit .
- That 's invented . - Ah , no , no , no .
- There 's no way that happened . - No he really believed it .
It was not intended for publication . So , why invent it ?
I think whoever did the transcripts
must have adapted them , filled in the gaps .
So , like stenography ? Kind of .
Yeah , that 's a good analogy .
But if you 're interested ,
there 's a TV movie from the sixties that depicts the séance .
It 's really tacky , but seems accurate .
I 'll find the title for you , but if you type in like :
" Hugo + Jersey + Turning Tables " on YouTube , you will find it .
Crazy dog , aren 't you ?
" Victor Hugo in Jersey . "
The being called the white lady asked me on the first day a thing that I did .
I know that a being , afraid of coming , ran away .
Is there someone here ?
If yes knock once ...
If no knock twice .
Before I ask you who you are , I 'll ask you a question .
But first , this question , do you see it in my thoughts ?
Do you want to answer it ?
Then talk .
The mountain is my grave .
I 'm God 's breath , I go up and down , I want the sky and the Earth wants me .
The stars pull me by my hair and the nails of the coffin hold me by my feet .
The darkness screams to me : " Down ! " And the Sun says " Up ! " to me .
I 'm the uncomforted of the horizon .
I 'm the night watcher of countless graves ,
emptying his eyes in empty skulls .
I 'm the cause of bad dreams .
Vincent can see the plain .
That is a reason .
I 'm everywhere but I 'm not sure what .
I get up and go to bed .
Unknown : Send me a picture .
I prefer you like this .
I feel ridiculous , it 's not me .
I 'm ashamed of myself .
I don 't know why I came .
Keep the key . You 'll be coming back .
- Excuse me . - Yes ?
I need to know what name was room 724 was booked under ?
Okay , just a second .
724 ...
It was ...
Maureen Cartwright , I have .
No , I 'm Maureen Cartwright . Who paid for the room ?
Just a sec .
I 'm sorry , there is no credit card information .
Was paid in advance in cash .
Do you remember if it was a man or a woman ?
I don 't know . I was not working at that moment .
Would you ask a colleague ? Do you know ... ?
It 's a big hotel .
I 'm not sure I can help you with that .
Thank you .
These are the five pieces of your selection .
And particularly the " Pont des Arts " of the " Paris Nouvelle " collection .
Made of 18 carat rose gold and fine stones .
C 'est bien . Yes , it 's perfect .
The necklace , the bracelet , the ring and the watch ,
but excluding this . I 've never seen that .
Okay . We 'll focus on these four .
- Okay . - I 'll prepare them for you then .
Merci .
You 're welcome .
And this one is brand new , first time released .
So nobody has it .
Oh , good . That 's important . Thank you .
Hey Kyra , you back ?
Sorry , I let myself in . I 'm just gonna drop these bags for you , okay ?
Hey Kyra , you doing alright ?
Hey ?
Are you ready ?
I drove for ...
2 minutes maybe before I realised what I was doing ,
And I came back and called .
Why didn 't you do it earlier ?
I-I-I ... I freaked out .
I-I-I ran away .
You ran away from a presence ...
There way a light on in the ...
back of the apartment , I heard something .
What were you doing at Mrs. Gellman 's ?
Dropping off a couple of bags .
I don 't understand .
I 'm a personal shopper . She was ...
very high profile and couldn 't ...
do normal things , didn 't have time .
And I sort of assisted her in that .
You used Mrs. Gellman 's computer last night .
Um , maybe .
And again this morning .
You check your messages on Gmail .
We have the record .
So , why are you asking ?
Did you sleep at her place ?
Yes , I did . I slept at her place .
Why ?
Um , I don 't know .
To be honest , I never do that .
Why did you hide it ?
A stupid reaction .
Maybe , maybe I was ...
a little ashamed .
You knew she was coming home today ?
Yeah . She was coming back from Milan ,
and on her way to Marrakech .
I was dropping off some accessories for her .
What accessories ?
Jewellery .
What jewellery ?
Very expensive jewellery from Cartier .
And you left it there ?
Yeah . In four cases in two bags .
Were they still there when you went back ?
I-I-I don 't know . I wasn 't ...
I wasn 't considering the jewellery at that point ...
I didn 't notice .
Unknown : Did you tell the cops about my texts ?
Unknown : ANSWER ME .
Unknown : DID YOU TELL THE COPS ABOUT MY TEXTS ?
Sorry , if I woke you up .
I was just stress-testing ...
one of the new security protocols .
Really fucking hard to configure .
So , it 's gonna take me a month .
Best case .
I 'm gonna come see you .
You giving up ?
Yeah , it 's not going to happen .
Maureen , it 's not that it isn 't going to happen ,
it 's that it doesn 't exist .
After death ,
there 's nothing .
I - I know .
And it 's not that big a deal .
You told me that you had a hope ...
Like you really hoped that ...
Of course I do .
But , no .
I don 't believe .
I don 't want to be here anymore .
I don 't want to be in Paris anymore .
I miss you .
I miss you too .
I 'm actually heading up the mountains for a few days .
If you want to , you can come quickly and meet me there .
Maybe ...
It really depends on what the police say .
If the travel ban 's been lifted or not .
The police ?
Yeah , Kyra was murdered , you didn 't hear that ?
- It 's everywhere . All over the news . - What ?
- I found her . - Murdered ?
Who murdered her ?
I don 't know .
It was really horr ... It was , ah ...
Are you okay ?
I can 't talk about it . It was fucking horrible .
You want me to call you back later ?
I 'll call you .
Unknown : Crown Plaza . Room 329 . Right away .
Unknown : I 'll wait another hour .
Unknown : I know you are reading my texts . Come .
Unknown : Then I 'll come .
Unknown : I have spares of your keys .
Unknown : I am in the taxi .
Unknown : I am in front of your building .
Unknown : Come down .
Unknown : Now .
Unknown : I am coming up .
Unknown : I am on the landing .
- You okay ? - Yeah .
- They ... Can I have some ? - Yeah , sure .
They arrested Ingo , and he ...
and he confessed to everything .
Did they lift the travel ban ?
Yeah . The case is closed .
But you 'll testify ?
Yes , yeah , probably .
Do you want to come to my place ?
Yeah . I feel , um ...
I 'm scared when I alone now .
You 're going to see Gary , right ?
Yes , Yep .
You should have gone a while ago .
I should have listened to you .
Let 's go , I have my car .
- Morning . - Morning .
You 're Lewis ' sister ?
I am .
We were together at l 'École Boulle .
Now I work at the Gobelin workshops .
Actually , I should get going soon .
You should stay .
If you can .
- Maureen . - Erwin .
Both : Enchanté .
I understand that you might feel uncomfortable .
Why ?
Because I 've taken Lewis ' place .
So soon .
Not at all .
You 're mistaken .
While he was alive , there was nothing between Lara and me .
It didn 't cross my mind . Honestly .
You know how they say , the dead watch over the living ?
I 've thought about that quite a lot .
Not just because Lewis was a medium .
I don 't know what that means .
For me , he was someone deeply intuitive of others .
He understood things that went unspoken .
He did .
Maybe because he knew he was going to die .
I mean I felt that he saw things which I didn 't .
Maybe you do too .
He thought that you had the same gifts .
I don 't know .
I , ah ..
Had a tendency to follow him .
He took things quite far .
Too far for me , at least .
I couldn 't keep up .
All I mean is that with Lewis ,
nothing seems impossible .
Many religions believe that the soul wanders around for a while
before leaving this world .
Did he speak to you about that ?
He was convinced of it .
Years ago , Mum died ,
he was sure that ...
he was visited by her . That she came to say goodbye to him .
That it felt like a dream , but not , that it was very real .
He could smell her , he could see her so clearly ... you know ?
Do you believe that ?
Yeah , I do .
It 's not a religion thing , but I ...
I do .
Do you think Lewis is here ?
I don 't think so .
I feel his presence .
He 's here .
That might be your guilt talking .
You don 't need to feel guilty .
Lara deserves to be happy .
And you do too .
I like to think so but ...
something is stopping me .
- I hope it has nothing to do with me . - No .
But you also have to free yourself of Lewis .
Well , I wish he 'd let me .
Wherever he is ,
he would never forbid it .
And even if he 's nowhere ,
hold onto the memory of his freedom .
Put it into practice .
I know what you mean .
You know , I have to get going .
Will you be staying a few days ?
Just tonight . I leave tomorrow .
- So , I 'll see you tonight . - Okay .
Uhh , uhh uhh . Good boy .
What happened ?
A glass broke .
I thought you were outside ?
Erwin just left .
He must have left it on the edge of the table , or something .
I hope you had a good trip .
Get some rest .
Your driver is named Salim .
It 's best to leave a little before daybreak .
Count on a five hour ride .
Don 't worry , the road is safe , even if it is not very busy .
Take the minimum . I have everything we need .
In other words , not much .
If it 's okay with you , we 'll stay for a week .
You 'll have to be tolerant , it 's spartan .
But you told me this is what you wanted .
Haiji ?
Lewis ?
Are you here ?
Have you been waiting for me ?
Are you at peace ?
Thank you .
Are you not at peace ?
Are you playing with me ?
Do you mean harm ?
I don 't know you .
Who are you ?
Lewis , is it you ?
Or is it just me ?
Translation and subtitles by PEPPER LALASPAIN * * * SONG LIVES FOR EVER * * *